[{"answer": " Did you see the Rockets game yesterday", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Yeah.  They crushed the Nicks", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Did you see the Rockets game yesterday", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " The score was 85 to 55.  The Nicks really stink", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Yeah.  They crushed the Nicks", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " I dont know what happened this season.  Last season they did all right, but thi", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 15, "question": " The score was 85 to 55.  The Nicks really stink", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Didnt they get a lot of new team members", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 19, "question": " I dont know what happened this season.  Last season they did all right, but thi", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": "Yes, they got like five new players in the NBA draft", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Didnt they get a lot of new team members", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Maybe they just need more time to practice as a team with the new players", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 21, "question": "Yes, they got like five new players in the NBA draft", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Who knows", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Maybe they just need more time to practice as a team with the new players", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " The Rockets really were amazing last night though.  Did you see that guy Yao", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Who knows", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Yeah, isnt he the center", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 24, "question": " The Rockets really were amazing last night though.  Did you see that guy Yao", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Yep, thats him.  Hes hard to miss.  Do you know how tall he is", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Yeah, isnt he the center", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " How tall", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Yep, thats him.  Hes hard to miss.  Do you know how tall he is", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": "Seven foot six and a half", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 30, "question": " How tall", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Hes huge", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Seven foot six and a half", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " I know.  And hes only 27", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Hes huge", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Is he Asian-American", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 33, "question": " I know.  And hes only 27", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " No, hes Chinese.  Hes from China.  He used to play ball for a Shanghai tea", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Is he Asian-American", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Well, hes really popular in America now.  Hes a spokesperson for McDonalds", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 38, "question": " No, hes Chinese.  Hes from China.  He used to play ball for a Shanghai tea", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Yeah, Ive seen lots of his commercials on TV", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Well, hes really popular in America now.  Hes a spokesperson for McDonalds", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Im sure he has millions of dollars", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Yeah, Ive seen lots of his commercials on TV", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Well, he deserves it.  Hes a great player on the team.  He makes a lot o", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Im sure he has millions of dollars", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": "Hes really skilled at handling rebounds too.  He gets in there and steals the ball", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Well, he deserves it.  Hes a great player on the team.  He makes a lot o", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Did you see when he snatched the ball yesterday during the last 10 seconds an", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Hes really skilled at handling rebounds too.  He gets in there and steals the ball", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " That was awesome.  Well, he should be good.  He comes from basketball", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Did you see when he snatched the ball yesterday during the last 10 seconds an", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 54, "question": " That was awesome.  Well, he should be good.  He comes from basketball", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Both his mom and dad are over six feet tall and were professional basketbal", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 55, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Both his mom and dad are over six feet tall and were professional basketbal", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Yep.  And his wife is even a Chinese basketball player too", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Basketball must be in their blood", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Yep.  And his wife is even a Chinese basketball player too", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Theyll probably have tall, basketball-playing kids too", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Basketball must be in their blood", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Hes got to get through the season before he has any kids", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Theyll probably have tall, basketball-playing kids too", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " There are still 12 games left", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Hes got to get through the season before he has any kids", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " I love basketball season, man", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 68, "question": " There are still 12 games left", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Me too.  I constantly have my TV turned to a game", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 69, "question": " I love basketball season, man", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Me too.  Its driving my girlfriend crazy", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Me too.  I constantly have my TV turned to a game", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Maybe we should start going out to a bar to watch the games", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Me too.  Its driving my girlfriend crazy", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " We should.  Well give the girls their TVs back and well go get some beer an", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Maybe we should start going out to a bar to watch the games", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Sounds like a plan", "docId": "08-04", "aSentId": 76, "question": " We should.  Well give the girls their TVs back and well go get some beer an", "qSentId": 75}]
